all right yeah let's bring the house
down on the ground you've been
looking for TV show what it can found
they'll make you cheer for the sound
can't find any DVDs we'll ask around
I've loved walking sock on the ground
every time it's on TV every time it's on
I wanna say we Manic ‘n Sonia you don't
get better than this if you think
otherwise it's my ass you're gonna kiss
all the sweet little girls and boys
fought through the streets listen to
them sick Sonic Underground beats Sonic
Underground taught me how to love it
showed me the light who the DAO yo yo yo
it's like Underground you've been
looking with TV show what it's them
found some thoughts on Sonic Manic and
Sonia you don't get better than this if
you think otherwise it's my acid gonna
kid
Sonic on the ground is really cool you
can take it from me I know for so long